<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nuts Pub Crawls London</title>
    <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nuts Pub Crawls London</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nutspubcrawl.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A guide to London for expats</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog-guide/</guid>
      <description>Housing in London
 We’ve gathered a range of sites, organisations and tips to help you find accommodation depending on the length of your stay&amp;nbsp;
More information       Passport What to do? How long will it take and what documents do I need to show upon arrival?
More information      Opening a bank account What for? Where to go, how to get one, how to transfer my money; these are the questions we answer in this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/about/</guid>
      <description>How does it work?      The pub crawl takes place 4 evenings a week, from Wednesday to Saturday. You can book your tickets online or at the door. There is no need to print it, you can show it on your mobile. Join us at the meeting point (the address is written on the ticket) and the guide will give you a wristband that will give you access to all the clubs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Au Pairs in London</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/au-pairs-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/au-pairs-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Hello girls and guys ! As a former au pair, i know that it is usual to ask many questions about this kind of job. That’s why i’m going to try to answer it with objectivity and candor.
What is an au pair? An au pair has to take care of children in a foreign family. In exchange, this family will nourish and host her/him and will make sure that the au pair feels integrated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/contact/</guid>
      <description> Don’t hesitate to get in touch </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding a job in London</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/finding-a-job-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/finding-a-job-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Like most expatriates, you are looking for a job. We will give you a few tips to help you get started. Before you start looking for a job, you will have to get your National Insurance Number. This document does not give you the right to work but insures you in the same way as a British person. Once your NIN is obtained, begin the process of opening a bank account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding an internship in London</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/finding-an-internship-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/finding-an-internship-in-london/</guid>
      <description>If you have to do an internship as part of your studies and you like the look of London, or you want to take advantage of it to improve your English without going to the other end of the earth, then this article is for you! We’ve also been through this in the editing team so we have some little tips for you.
Where to look  Start by updating your CV in English as well as your cover letter If you are lucky enough that your school offers you internships, do not set them aside with the thought of being able to find better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Pub Crawl</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/foxpubcrawl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/foxpubcrawl/</guid>
      <description>London Pub Crawls Follow the leaders and party in different venues during your best night out in London!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare in London</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/healthcare-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/healthcare-in-london/</guid>
      <description>How to find your General Practioner (GP)? To access healthcare as we have it back at home, you will need to register with a General Practitioner, or GP. In England this works by area, i.e. your GP will be the one who lives closest to you (according to your post code), so it is easy to find them, you can go to the National Health Service site and search using your post code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Housing in London</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/housing-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/housing-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Finding housing that matches the length of your stay, budget and area desired
Prerequisite: internet, a little patience and some savviness.
Staying less than 14 days For a short stay we recommend the following solutions: Youth hostels, Airbnb, student halls and couchsurfing
Youth Hostels London&amp;rsquo;s youth hostels are getting cooler through time. Those that we will advise you are clean, secure, and have bars inside, making it easy to meet other travellers and socialise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London&#39;s airports</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/londons-airports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/londons-airports/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Heathrow, Gatwick or Stansted? There are 5 airports in London surrounding the capital and in all of them you can find transport services that will take you to the centre. In this blog we summarise how to get around in each airport it’s clearer and easier upon your arrival. 
London Heathrow (LHR) &amp;hellip;is the closest airport to the centre (25km) and busiest too but you will not have any difficulty in reaching central London, which you can do in a variety of ways:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Insurance Number</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/national-insurance-number/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/national-insurance-number/</guid>
      <description>The NIN, what’s that about&amp;hellip;? The National Insurance Number, equivalent to our French social security, will allow you to work in England, it will be asked of you automatically and is essential. As always the steps vary depending on the case, and here it depends on whether you already have a job or are still looking. A little more explanation?
I have a job! We&amp;rsquo;ll start with the lucky ones who have already found a job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opening a bank account in London</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/opening-a-bank-account-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/opening-a-bank-account-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Why? You will need to open a bank account here, especially if your French bank takes commissions for every withdrawal/payment (inquire before departure), but also to be able to receive your salary. The procedures differ by bank, online or traditional, if you begin the paperwork before departure or in person&amp;hellip; In short, here are some pointers that will certainly clear things up for you.
Where? First, opening your account remotely is possible, you can start this type of approach with your French bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our tours</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/tours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/tours/</guid>
      <description>CENTRAL LONDON NUTS PUB CRAWL Pub crawl run in central London. You will visit the best clubs around Leicester Square and Piccadilly Circus. All clubs are within a 5 minute walk.
 TICKETS      THE SHOREDITCH PUB CRAWL This tour takes place in the district of Shoreditch. The guides will take you around Old Street and Shoreditch. All venues are within walking distance.&amp;nbsp;
 TICKETS         NIGHT WALKING TOURS Bringing you from Westminster To Piccadilly Circus and end in One of the best London central club</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/photos/</guid>
      <description>You’ll find all of our photos on the photo site: PHOTOS        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party in London</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/party-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/party-in-london/</guid>
      <description>The city of London is known to be very expensive, whether it be the price of housing or access to the various clubs called &amp;ldquo;trendy&amp;rdquo;. We are going to tell you about the most friendly and good-value places, and then we&amp;rsquo;ll talk a bit more about the clubs in some of the most famous neighborhoods of the capital such as Soho, Brixton and Shoreditch.
Leicester Square / Piccadilly good deals It is sometimes difficult to get out in the capital when there is a lack of money, so I have listed for you the best plans to enjoy the nightlife that London is famous for !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passports in London</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/passports-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/passports-in-london/</guid>
      <description>The United Kingdom is still part of the EU, so for the time being ID cards are enough for Europeans and French nationals to visit. However, if you plan on staying in London for a while, we advise you to have a passport to be prepared for any eventuality, and if you do not know how to do so, don’t panic.
What to do There are two scenarios: those who have to renew their passport and those who are applying for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tickets</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/tickets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/tickets/</guid>
      <description>London Pub Crawls Follow the leader and party in different venues during your best night out in London !!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transport in London</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/transport-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/transport-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Mind the gap! When you arrive in London, you will quickly realize that the cost of transport is extremely high. To find out how much you are going to have to pay per month for you to move to the capital, we&amp;rsquo;ve put together a little summary for you:
Visitor Oyster Card: This is the cheapest way for single trips. A so-called ‘smart’ plastic card, it works with the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tropics global college</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/tropicsglobalcollege/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/tropicsglobalcollege/</guid>
      <description>London Pub Crawls Follow the leaders and party in different venues during your best night out in London!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful apps to download in London</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/useful-apps-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/blog/useful-apps-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Arriving in the most densely populated capital of Europe, you have to adapt, so we’ve put together a top list of essential apps to have to hand when settling in London.
Find your way Apps  CityMapper: To know where you are going, you could use the GPS already installed on your phone, but when you start to use it, you will understand. For all your journeys, the app calculates the optimal route for you, depending on your preferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eazycity</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/eazycity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/eazycity/</guid>
      <description>London Pub Crawls Follow the leaders and party in different venues during your best night out in London!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>londonnest</title>
      <link>https://nutspubcrawl.com/londonnest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nutspubcrawl.com/londonnest/</guid>
      <description>London Pub Crawls Follow the leaders and party in different venues during your best night out in London!!!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>